<right>
<titulo>PKU gel</titulo>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3 align="left">Indications</h3>
<p>A phenylalanine free gel or drink for use in the dietary management of Phenylketonuria in children from 12 months to 10 years of age. </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Product Features</h3>
<ul>
    <li>Phenylalanine free </li>
    <li>Contains the necessary mixture of amino acids, carbohydrates, minerals, trace elements and vitamins to meet the daily nutritional needs of this age group </li>

    <li>Provides 42g of protein equivalent per 100g of powder </li>
    <li>Designed to be made into a gel or low volume drink </li>
    <li>Available as orange, raspberry or unflavored powder </li>
    <li>Convenient and great tasting </li>
</ul>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Nutritional Information &amp; Ingredients</h3>

<p>Available for download at the end of this page.</p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Important Information</h3>
<p>PKU gel must only be given to patients with proven Phenylketonuria and under strict medical supervision. It is not recommended for infants under 12 months of age or as a sole source of nutrition. <strong>PKU gel is not for parenteral use.</strong></p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Dosage and Administration</h3>
<ul>
    <li>Dosage of PKU gel should be determined by the clinician or dietitian. </li>
    <li>The daily protein requirement is given as PKU gel (100g is equivalent to 42g of protein). </li>
    <li>Additional protein is provided from natural protein sources containing 50mg of phenylalanine. The number of daily portions is adjusted according to plasma phenylalanine concentrations. </li>

    <li>Foods high in carbohydrate and fat but low in protein should be provided as an energy source to supply the remainder of daily calories. </li>
</ul>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Guidelines for Preparation and Use</h3>
<p>PKU gel can be taken as a gel or as a low volume drink</p>
<ol>
    <li>Empty the contents of a sachet into a beaker (provided) and add cold water – 30ml for a gel or half way up the beaker (100ml) for a drink. Secure the lid and shake for 10 seconds. For the gel, let stand for 2 minutes. For the drink, serve immediately. </li>
    <li>Water or permitted drinks should be taken after the PKU gel. </li>
    <li>Cover and refrigerate any unused formula. Use prepared formula within 24 hours.&nbsp; Shake well before serving. </li>

</ol>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
 <h3>Storage</h3>
<p>Store unopened sachets at room temperature. After opening, store tightly sealed sachet in a cool, dry place and use within one month. Avoid storing product in areas of extreme temperatures. </p>
<p></p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<p>
<table summary="This table displays the product availability">
    <caption>Availability</caption>
    <tbody>
        <tr>
            <th>Product </th><th>&nbsp;Packaging</th><th>Reimbursement Code</th><th>HCPCS Code</th>

        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>PKU gel unflavored</td>
            <td>30 x 20g sachets</td>
            <td>5060014051202</td>
            <td>
            <p align="left">B4162</p>

            </td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>PKU gel orange</td>
            <td>30 x 20g sachets</td>
            <td>
            <p align="left">5060014051264</p>

            </td>
            <td>
            <p align="left">B4162</p>
            </td>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>PKU gel raspberry</td>
            <td>30 x 20g sachets</td>

            <td>
            <p align="left">5060014051233</p>
            </td>
            <td>
            <p align="left">B4162</p>
            </td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>

</table>
</p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
 <div id="ProductContainer_ProductDetail_CliniciansDownloads" class="downloads">
<h2>Downloads - Clinicians</h2>
<ul>

<li class="first pdf"><a href="http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//3/1/316c3dc4-0dd5-4ca7-b065-6e2021277321.pdf">PKU gel Nutritional Information &amp; Ingredients</a><span class="i"> 93.2 KB pdf</span></li>

<li class="first pdf"><a href="http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//4/6/460c9c19-2306-4b2e-b699-396d37d2ad2a.pdf">Metabolic Sample Request Form</a><span class="i"> 64.7 KB pdf</span></li>

</ul>
</div><!-- downloads -->
	 ]]>
	</item>
</right>