<right>
<titulo>MSUD Express Cooler</titulo>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
     <h3><b>Indications</b></h3>
<p>A leucine, isoleucine, and valine free protein substitute for use in the dietary management of Maple Syrup Urine Disease (MSUD) in individuals aged 8 years and older.</p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Product Features </h3>
<ul type="disc">
    <li>Leucine, isoleucine, and valine free </li>

    <li>Ready to drink </li>
    <li>Low volume and low calorie </li>
    <li>Contains the necessary mixture of amino acids, carbohydrates, minerals, trace elements and vitamins to meet the daily nutritional needs of this age group </li>
    <li>Provides 15g of protein equivalent per 130ml pouch </li>
    <li>Great tasting orange flavor </li>
</ul>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Nutrition Information &amp; Ingredients </h3>
<p>Available for download at the end of this page</p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Caution </h3>
<p>MSUD express cooler must only be given to patients with proven Maple Syrup Urine Disease and under strict medical supervision. It is not recommended for children under 8 years of age or as a sole source of nutrition. The product does contain a source of phenylalanine. MSUD express cooler is not for parenteral use. <br/>
</p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Dosage and Administration </h3>
<ul>

    <li>Dosage of MSUD express cooler should be determined by the clinician or dietitian </li>
    <li>The daily protein requirement is given as MSUD express cooler (130ml is equivalent to 15g of protein). </li>
    <li>Additional protein is provided from natural protein sources in medically prescribed quantities to provide leucine, isoleucine, and valine in controlled amounts, which is essential for normal development. </li>
    <li>Foods high in carbohydrate and fat but low in protein should be provided as an energy source to supply the remainder of daily calories. </li>
    <li>A supplement of isoleucine and valine is given if required (if plasma concentrations fall too low). </li>
</ul>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
 <h3>Guidelines for Preparation and Use </h3>

<p>MSUD express cooler comes in ready to drink sport pack. Simply shake before serving, open the screw top and drink. Product may be refrigerated for up to 24 hours after opening. MSUD express cooler can also be placed in the freezer the night before serving and defrosted the following morning by leaving the drink pack at room temperature for 2&frac12; hours. </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<h3>Storage </h3>
<p>Store unopened drink packs at room temperature. The product can be chilled in the refrigerator the day before serving as it is delicious cold. Avoid storing products in areas of extreme heat and direct sunlight.</p>
<p>
<table summary="This table displays the product availability">
    <caption>Availability</caption>
    <tbody>
        <tr>

            <th>Product Number </th><th>Description </th><th>Packaging </th><th>NDC Format Code </th>
        </tr>
        <tr>
            <td>054654</td>
            <td>MSUD express cooler orange</td>
            <td>30 x 130ml </td>

            <td>50600-0546-54</td>
        </tr>
    </tbody>
</table>
</p></p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
<div id="ProductContainer_ProductDetail_CliniciansDownloads" class="downloads">
<h2>Downloads - Clinicians</h2>
<ul>

<li class="first pdf"><a href='http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//a/0/a0203ce4-2c38-4f77-a6dd-16f62071df3d.pdf'>MSUD express cooler - nutritional information</a><span class="i"> 83.8 KB pdf</span></li>

<li class="first pdf"><a href='http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//4/6/460c9c19-2306-4b2e-b699-396d37d2ad2a.pdf'>Metabolic Sample Request Form</a><span class="i"> 64.7 KB pdf</span></li>
</ul>
</div><!-- downloads -->
	 ]]>
	</item>
</right>