<right>
<titulo>PKU Cooler System Cooler 20</titulo>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Indications</h3>
      <p>
       A phenylalanine free protein substitute for use in the dietary management of Phenylketonuria in people aged 3 years and older.
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Product Features</h3>
      <p>
      <ul>
        <li>Phenylalanine free</li>
        <li>Low volume and ready to drink</li>
        <li>Contains the necessary mixture of amino acids, carbohydrates, minerals, trace elements and vitamins to meet the daily nutritional needs of this age group</li>
        <li>Provides 20g of protein equivalent per 174 ml pouch</li>
        <li>Available in orange and purple flavors</li>
        <li>Convenient, easy and great tasting</li>
      <ul>
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Nutritional Information &amp; Ingredients</h3>
      <p>
       Available for download at the end of this page.
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Caution</h3>
      <p>
       PKU cooler20 must only be given to patients with proven Phenylketonuria and under strict medical supervision.&nbsp; It is not recommended for children under 3 years of age. PKU cooler20 is not for parenteral use.
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Dosage and Administration</h3>
      <p>
        <li>Dosage of PKU cooler20 should be determined by the clinician or dietitian</li>
        <li>The daily protein requirement is given as PKU cooler20.</li>
        <li>Additional protein is provided form exchanges of natural protein in medically prescribed quantities, to provide phenylalanine in controlled amounts, which is essential for normal growth and development.</li>
        <li>Foods high in carbohydrate and fat but low in protein should be provided as an energy source to supply the remainder of daily calories.</li>
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Guidelines for Preparation and Use</h3>
      <p>
       PKU cooler20 comes in ready to drink sport pack.&nbsp; Simply shake before serving, open the screw top and drink.&nbsp; Product may be refrigerated for up to 24 hours after opening.&nbsp; PKU cooler20 can also be placed in the freezer the night before serving and defrosted the following morning by leaving the drink pack at room temperature for 2 &frac12; hours.
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Storage</h3>
      <p>
       Store unopened drink packs at room temperature.&nbsp; The product can be chilled in the refrigerator the day before serving as it is delicious cold.&nbsp; Avoid storing products in areas of extreme heat and direct sunlight.
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <p>
        <table summary="This table displays the product availability">
            <caption>Availability</caption>
            <tbody>
                <tr>

                    <th>Product Number </th><th>Description </th><th>Packaging </th><th>NDC Format Code </th>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>054814</td>
                    <td>PKU cooler20 orange</td>
                    <td>30 x&nbsp;174 ml</td>

                    <td>50600-0548-14</td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                    <td>054838</td>
                    <td>PKU cooler20 purple</td>
                    <td>30 x&nbsp;174 ml</td>

                    <td>50600-0548-38</td>
                </tr>
            </tbody>
        </table>
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <![CDATA[
      <h3 align="left">Downloads - Clinicians</h3>
      <p>
        <ul>
        <li class="first pdf"><a href='http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//4/6/460c9c19-2306-4b2e-b699-396d37d2ad2a.pdf'>Metabolic Sample Request Form</a><span class="i"> 64.7 KB pdf</span></li>
        <li class="first pdf"><a href='http://www.vitaflousa.com/Resources//0/0/00c80cfd-84bc-4ed0-90d5-dae7374bf9c2.pdf'>PKU cooler20 - nutritional information</a><span class="i"> 89.4 KB pdf</span></li>
        </ul>
      </p>
	 ]]>
	</item>
</right>